by H.
me
Here we go, Bananamo, host of NogizakaKochichi-chu, thank you very much for your cooperation.
I'm Bananamo, your host in Kochi, Nogizaka.
I know it's a little off the air, but thank you so much for the live show.
Thank you so much for your hard work!
There's a member I talked to. We didn't see each other after the concert.
I wanted to talk to some of the members who were still popping up, but we ran out of time.
He also told us never to go down that weird hallway, that we couldn't get in, and that the only way to get in was for everyone to come.
We had a talk in a small area, and we laughed and laughed and laughed.
That's for sure. Today, Mr. Himura, please tell us what you're going to do.
It's going to be fun today. I'll let you in on a little secret.
Tonight, we'll just recommend our personal favorites and what we're into.
The member who impresses the chief judge, Mr. Himura, the most will be crowned queen of the month.
You know, with a body as big as Nogizaka's, there's a chance that you don't even know who's into what.
If I mention it here, maybe it'll go viral, or maybe some of you will giggle and say it's already trendy.
I'll decide on the queen this month, so take notes, Mr. Himura.
Please listen!
What's Kubo's favorite thing right now?
Kubo seems to know a lot of things. She's on the radio, too.
But if she's going to say something like that, she might as well say the Rakuten Eagles.
Well, that's okay, it's just what I like... but I've got something new for you today.
Here's what I'd like to introduce today!
Dalan Salt Marumaru
Salt and Sun...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Salt marumaru type.
It was popular for a while, but I especially like salted bread.
I love it!
I eat it too.
You do?
It's so good when it's freshly baked!
I love salted bread so much I go to specialty stores.
I know a lot about it, but I know a really good place that I don't want to tell you about.
I'm thinking of trying something different today.
It's a little bit of a problem with the current assessment, isn't it?
Why don't you tell me your number one?
I'll tell you later.
Oh, no.
People watching TV are gonna say, "Hey.
You like salt marbles in general?
I like all kinds of salted marumaru, but I'm going to recommend...
I hope it's salted Daifuku.
It's good, but...
But not the original salt!
Here it is!
MUJI Salted Caramel Nut Ice Cream
Ice cream?
That's right.
Do you know who this is?
Go ask who?
No, Kubo, no one knows.
You've all lost your lives.
Do you have ice cream?
MUJI does have ice cream, but sometimes their snacks are a big hit.
I love MUJI.
I go to MUJI in Ginza once a week.
Seriously?
I really love it.
I'm sure you wear clothes with more of a Muji stamp.
I even wear Muji clothes.
I really love Muji.
Muji, Muji, Muji.
Then I came across this salted caramel nut ice cream.
I don't know.
Actually, that's right, MUJI offers several kinds of ice cream.
I've had three different kinds, and this ice cream revolution has happened.
It's that good!
It's really good, but it's been a boom for a while now, and there was a time when it was a fix.
There was a period of time when it was a fixer-upper.
Is that so?
First of all, as a salt marumaru lover, I'm impressed.
But why did MUJI decide to make salted caramel nuts instead of just salted ice cream?
There are many salted vanilla ice cream products out there.
Yes, there is.
No, it's salted caramel.
But salted caramel is also salted caramel.
Yes, it is.
But ice cream...
But ice cream is not so easy to make, and I think it's genius that they made this combination.
When you hear it, you can imagine what it tastes like.
It's usually this kind of salted caramel.
I'm sorry, but I can.
I'm sorry, but I can do it.
I'll definitely overturn it.
I'm going to overturn it.
I'm sure we'll be able to top it.
I'm sure.
MUJI has another flavor of ice cream called hojicha that I like.
What's great about hojicha is that MUJI does a great job of reproducing the bitterness in their ice cream!
Ice cream for adults, isn't it?
That's right.
This salted caramel nut has just the right amount of bitter caramel and nuts that don't interfere with the bitter taste.
and the salt that complements the main ingredient.
It's the balance.
The salt is not the star of the show.
Salt plays a supporting role.
I have a rule that I eat Salt Marumaru on an empty stomach.
That's right.
I want you to eat it while feeling the balance of salt.
You can't have dessert after you eat.
Dessert is fine, but I want you to take a bath and open the door a little.
I want you to open the door and feel the salt with your senses sharpened.
That's a lot of passion.
The way you put it together is amazing!
The four of us will taste Kubo's new favorite ice cream!
I'm so happy for you, Saku-chan and Nagi-chan!
I'd like you to try Saku-chan Nagi-chan!
This type?
I thought it'd be this type or the candy type!
You've never had it?
I've never had it.
Oh, I feel like I've been hit.
You got me.
I love how Muji is so accessible.
I'm going to change my mind on my way home from the recording session today.
That's for sure.
Let's have Saku-chan and Nagi-chan eat first.
I don't think these two can explain.
It tastes the best.
I don't care.
Bon appétit!
The caramel.
Oh, it's delicious!
You don't have to say that.
There's quite a bit of bitterness.
Yes, it does.
What bitterness?
It tastes like burnt caramel.
The amount and size of the nuts are perfect.
I know exactly what you mean.
Do you feel the salt? Just a little bit of salt.
Just a little bit of salt.
I forgot to eat my lunch today.
I'm eating it in just the right state.
Sharpened.
In a well-honed state.
What do you mean you forgot to eat your lunch?
Inadvertently
What do you mean you forgot to eat this?
Delicious!
It makes you happy, doesn't it?
It's not what you think.
I really don't think it tastes like what you think it tastes like.
I'm serious.
Bon appétit.
Yum!
Wow, I'm so happy.
There was a good amount of nuts in there.
The amount and size of the nuts were perfect.Perfect amount and size of nuts.
That's nice.
It's really going to spread out.
That's right.
Salt? Salt.
A little bit.
I don't feel any salt.
No, you have to feel it.
The ice cream is complete when you feel the salt.
I see what you mean.
Slow down and concentrate.
You feel it?
I feel it.
The saltiness comes.
It's like a rush at the end.
Yes, there's a specific caramel taste.
Then the nutty taste comes in at the end.
And then the salt taste comes in.
Poof! Poof!
Poof!
You're gonna be surprised.
I don't know.
I like the salt.
Salt?
If you let it dissolve slowly...
You can feel the salt.
It's the balance of the saltiness.
It's good, but the ice cream...
It's delicious.
I wish more people knew about it.
You don't buy a lot of Muji ice cream, do you?
No, I've never had it.
Amazing.
Sugata, you eat this kind of ice cream?
I'm sure everyone has their own favorite ice cream.
We could have at least had ice cream today.
I could.
What kind of ice cream do you buy the most in your life?
Pinot.
What kind of ice cream do you eat the most?
Haagen-Dazs.
Haagen-Dazs what?
Vanilla.
Strawberry.
It's good, isn't it?
You're eating good food.
Yeah, but you're right.
It's a different generation, you know, when Häagen-Dazs was sold at Seven.
I see.
I always have some Häagen-Dazs on hand, of course.
Of course, I eat good food.
But you're different.
I eat Garigari-kun.
I'm eating "Garigari-kun".
That's Mr. Himura's Garigarikumi-kun.
It's good.
I'm glad.
It's like this... now.
I like it.
That's what I'm talking about.
I love it.
If it were on the radio, we'd talk about it for two hours.
We could do it now.
You've definitely done it.
That's great.
Next, what's Shibata's current favorite?
What's Shibata going to introduce to us already?
Sweet things go well together.
I don't mean grandma and grandpa or anything.
I'm grateful for the introductions, though.
I'll introduce you to...
A quilt.
What? Surprising.
Why is this like a mail order?
No, no, no, I'm sure everyone uses a comforter.
This isn't a nonstop show.
What are you doing with your comforter?
I'm hanging it up.
How are you doing, Mr. Kimura?
I'm hanging up the comforter.
What do you do with your comforter?
What do you use?
A comforter.
Just one?
One.
What do you do with it, Mr. Okada?
This is a blanket. It's sold by mail order nonstop.
It's called a heat loop, and it's like a futon on top.
I'm in the middle of it.
You asked me if I'd like to introduce you to something.
I'd like to introduce to you...
A weighted blanket!
What's a weighted blanket?
As the name suggests, it's a heavy comforter.
What? A futon is heavy?
It's not light.
Do you know what it is?
You know someone who does, don't you?
Yes, I know.
So does Ume.
I use the heavy one.
You do?
What? Is that what's popular here?
When I wanted to get a good night's sleep.
I was looking it up on the Internet.
I was looking it up on the Internet, and I came across it.
That's right.
It depends on the person.
But I've been looking for something light and fluffy.
A light futon is light.
That's right.
Have you ever heard of a heavy futon?
There's a good thing about heavy futons.
The comfortable weight is a little like the weight of a person.
It's that heavy?
I don't know... it gives you a sense of security.
Like you're being hugged?
That's what I mean.
It's a comfortable weight that makes you feel safe.
I'm curious.
It bothers me a lot.
And the other nice thing is, when you wake up in the morning...
When you wake up in the morning, does the bedclothes fall out of the bed?
or the middle of the bedding falls out of the bed?
I know, I know, I know.
I'm not a good sleeper either, and I used to wake up in the morning and find my quilt
I used to wake up and find my comforter on the floor.
But since I started using this, even the comforter is here when I wake up in the morning.
Is it that heavy?
I'm going to be in bed and I'm going to be like, "Argh!
Yeah, I guess.
Isn't it possible?
Let's see what Shibata likes now.
Try Yodagu on a weighted blanket.
Yoda, you know this?
I've never heard of it.
But I use a light one, and when I wake up in the morning, I'm not wearing it.
Not wearing?
Futon.
Some people take it all off.
It's heavy.
Can you hold it?
It's so heavy.
Is it that heavy?
It looks heavy.
It's heavier than it is now.
It's like the training ritual of Monkey King or something.
It's not like a normal futon.
It's like a medium-sized dog.About a medium-sized dog
huh?
Oh, my God.
No way.
Please hold it.
Okay, Yoda, try sleeping for a bit.
I got it.
It looks good on you.
It looks good on you
It's true.
That's true.
Is it heavy?
It's heavy.
Heavy.
It's a comfortable weight.
Really.
Seriously.
It's really good.
Doesn't it hurt?
No, not at all. It feels like it's holding me in place.
It's... it's warm to begin with.
It's warm.
I chose the ones that have a winter front and a summer back, so they can be used all year round.
You're right.
You put the back of this on?
Wow, that's the newest thing.
I want one.
Seriously.
I like that you can't roll over too much.
Is it that heavy?
I want to roll over.
I want to roll over... on my body.
Hey, Yoda, we're gonna sleep with you, okay?
Can we come in?
Oh, my God.
Really?
I think the first one's the big one.
I think the bar has been raised.
It's like a little one-handed tug.
Not even close.
It's so heavy!
I'm sorry, it looks uncomfortable.
I can't sleep like this.
It's heavy!
It's a weapon.
It hurts! It hurts!
It's heavy.
Try to sleep.
Is it too heavy? Too heavy.
It's heavy.
Is it comfortable?
I don't know.
You won't know until you've slept on it for a few days.
Is it too heavy?
But the one I'm using is heavier.
Really? Just hold it.
Use maybe one of these heavier ones.
I'll never get a good night's sleep.
This one makes it hard.
Try it.
It's really comfortable.
No, it's heavy.
Try a little sleep.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, I'm not testing you.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a woman coming.
It's so heavy.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
I didn't think it was this heavy.
If you like to be held, you'll love this.
Someone bring her a Sea Pap.
We have to put the Sea Pup on.
No, you're right, if you like being held tight...
Oh, my God, it's like a grenade.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why are they laughing at me all the time?
I don't know.
I thought it looked like a grenade.
They were laughing before that.
It's like a grenade.
No, no, no, it's because it's the color of a grenade.
But I know, I know, I know.
Is there another one on top?
Yes, and two more.
Two more?
Because it's so heavy.
It's definitely warmer when it's heavier.
It's like being wrapped up in a blanket.
How much does it weigh?
Seven kilos.
That's heavy.
It's heavy.
No, it's just a little hard to fix the bedding.
Who was that?
I've loved the weight of a futon since I was a little girl.
I bought one recently and use it all the time.
I don't know, I just don't think about it.
I want you to feel how good it is to wake up in the morning.
I don't think you'll wake up well.
I want you to try it just for a day.
If you get used to it, you'll have a hard time staying at hotels and stuff.
If you get used to it, you'll have a hard time when you stay over at a hotel.
It's true that if you don't put the weights on yourself...
I'll have to put the weights on myself.
But it's interesting... I didn't know that.
After this, Yamashita's mysterious rock gap appeared!
Next, Yamashita brought his favorite thing.
I'd like to introduce it today!
What's that?
Do you know it?
It's garbage.
Ruler, ruler, ruler...
There's a lot of it.
Food.
Is this food?
I'll try to answer correctly.
Tick-tock, tick-tock.
Today I'd like to introduce you to...
What?
Dangmyun.
Tummymyung.
I don't know.
I don't know!
You know about plums?
I've had dumplings.
You've had it?
I'm glad you don't know.
I don't know anything about 5th graders.
You're right, they're young.
There's a dangmyun restaurant?
Dangmyung?
I'm with Ai Myung.
You have a dangmyeon shop?
We don't have a dangmyeon restaurant.
It's a Korean restaurant.
Korean restaurant.
It's pretty common in Shin-Okubo.
It's called "thick vermicelli.
It's like vermicelli.
It originated in China and is now quite popular in Korea.
It doesn't look good at all.It doesn't look good at all!
What's this? It's all the rage with young girls like Yamashita.
I only found out about it about 2 years ago.
So-called gluttonous YouTubers...
ASMR is all the rage these days.
That's how I found out about it.
Gluttonous YouTuber?
YouTuber with a big voice?
What is a YouTuber with a big voice?
Hello.
It's a pain in the ass, that YouTuber.
I saw a YouTuber who eats a lot of this.
I saw a video of a YouTuber who eats a lot of this.
I thought it looked really good.
If it's like vermicelli, you can eat that much no matter how much you eat.
As is? I'm not supposed to eat it like this, is that okay?
You're biting your tongue.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
They don't sell them in Japanese supermarkets.
It's a Maloney thing.
I have no idea.
Seriously, I don't know why I don't know.
I buy a lot of imported groceries from overseas.
Recently, Uber Eats...
They have it.
No, they don't.
I don't even know how to eat Korean food.
I don't know.
I don't know. It's stewed with tteokbokki or something like that, and it's served at Korean restaurants.
But it's not this thick, like japchae.
But when you boil it, it's totally different.
It becomes something else.
Don't they keep their shape?
It keeps this shape.
Like vermicelli, when it's dry, it looks delicious.
I see.
When you boil it, it becomes very tasty.
You'll see when you eat it.
Here's my favorite thing about Sanmei.
It goes with everything!
It doesn't go with everything.
Think of it as vermicelli.
Vermicelli goes well with Japanese seasoning.
I also like it with chige and chili sauce. Chige...
I love sundried rice vermicelli.
What do you put in it?
I often make it myself.
When I have a lot of leftovers, I put this in on the second day.
It's like vermicelli soup.
Here is my favorite way to eat it!
Rosé flavor
Do you know about the rosé flavor?
Rosé is that rosé?
Rosé is that rosé.
Do you know what rosé is?
Red, white and rosé.
Rosé is a kind of wine.
It's very popular in Korea.
It's a little bit creamy with gochujang (red pepper paste) and white sauce.
It's like food.
Yes, a spicy cream sauce.
You mean a red cream sauce, like rosé?
Yes, it is.
Really? Does everybody know about this?
Really? Really?
People know about the rosé flavor.
I eat a lot of rosé.
I feel like I'm a tourist.
Rosé.
I eat a lot of rosé.
I'm not someone who doesn't speak your language.
I'll eat.
Korean food?
I don't know.
It's just us and Yoda.
You know what Yoda tastes like?
No, I don't know.
Do you know what rosé tastes like?
I don't know.
I don't know any Yoda and Goki.
I don't know anything about litter and yodas and bananas.
It's not the latest thing.
It's not the latest thing, but it's something that's popular inside, and they sell sauces like this on the market.
I buy it at Cardi's or something.
Is it spicy?
It's a little spicy.
But it really goes with everything.
I usually fry onions and sausages with this sauce.
Yay sausage!
And the sausage goes well with Peyoung's, so it's perfect.
That's what I mean.
I love it too, and I definitely eat it once or twice a week.
It's so good!
It's delicious.
What is it?
I had some last night at 1 a.m. and I loved it.
No way.
It's very filling.
It's healthy and perfect for you.
I see.
The futon's getting heavy.
I'm eating this clear stuff.
If you put it back in hot water...
I don't know about this.
What a taste of Yamashita's homemade dangmyun!
Dangmyun made with Yamashita's recommended recipe!
Wow, what is this? Ugh, it's disgusting!
I don't know what it looks like!
I kinda like to eat it with pork sinew or something.
It smells so good, but it looks like...
Can I try some?
Sure, have some.
I've never had it before. It smells super delicious.
Bon appétit.
What is this? I'm drinking this stuff.
It's good, it's beautiful, not as good as konnyaku, but like konnyaku.
Yes, it has a nice crunchy texture.
It's good, it tastes good.
The sauce goes really well with it.
Yum, it's good!
What's this?
Try the sausage, too.
It's good. It's Coe's.
This? Thank you.
I got some of Koh's sausage.
It's good. Is it rosé?
This is rosé. You used rosé?
Yes, very tasty.
With leftovers from the fridge, I usually fry vegetables for 2 minutes, like stir-fry.
I'm like this. Amazing.
You should ask the members to put in whatever they like.
I'll sneak something in.
I don't know what's going on with you, Kakki.
Bon appétit Earl!
Why did you just say Earl?
Why did you just say "Earl"? Is this your first time?
It's my first time.
It's like a rice cake.
It's true, it's like a rice cake. It's like a rice cake.
What's it made of?
It's made of the same stuff as vermicelli.
Like eraser?
What's vermicelli for?
Is vermicelli more elastic? No, it's not.
No, this one's more squishy.
You don't say.
No?
How many of these do I have to boil?
How many?How many?
Stupid question
How many of these should I boil?
I overboil a lot.
They call me "Taro the Boil Man.
How many are you boiling?
I haven't boiled that many.
Wow. I don't know anything about this stuff.
You're on a really high level today.
Have you ever heard of Gosei Tangmyung?
No, I don't.
No, but I've never been locked in a room except for this show.
That's funny.
Thank you.
You should try the dang-myung, too.
Please do.
I'll start from the bottom.
Ta-da! What?
I'm sorry for talking to the camera.
I'm sorry I've been up late lately.
Please subscribe to our channel.